<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DX</title>
    <link>http://douxin13.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 00:23:50 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://douxin13.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>无线通信选题报告</title>
      <link>http://douxin13.github.io/post/%E8%A5%BF%E5%AE%89%E7%94%B5%E5%AD%90%E7%A7%91%E6%8A%80%E5%A4%A7%E5%A4%A7%E5%AD%A6_%E7%BD%91%E7%BB%9C%E8%90%A5%E9%94%80_%E5%A4%A7%E7%B1%BB%E6%8B%9B%E7%94%9F/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 00:23:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://douxin13.github.io/post/%E8%A5%BF%E5%AE%89%E7%94%B5%E5%AD%90%E7%A7%91%E6%8A%80%E5%A4%A7%E5%A4%A7%E5%AD%A6_%E7%BD%91%E7%BB%9C%E8%90%A5%E9%94%80_%E5%A4%A7%E7%B1%BB%E6%8B%9B%E7%94%9F/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;doa-estimation-for-different-antenna-array-structures:fb01a2df35ea3e36db0979b4f08f3ad1&#34;&gt;DOA Estimation for Different Antenna Array Structures&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-introduction:fb01a2df35ea3e36db0979b4f08f3ad1&#34;&gt;1.Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smart antennas have gained great interest among researchers during recent years,
and different antenna array structures have different characteristics, which are
applied to different situations. At the same time, DOA(Direction of Arrival) is a very
important parameter for smart antennas, and there are many algorithms to estimate
it. In this paper, what I focus on is DOA estimation for different array structures based
on MUSIC(Multiple Signal Classification) algorithm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-statement:fb01a2df35ea3e36db0979b4f08f3ad1&#34;&gt;2.Statement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For simplify, let [1], [2]and [3] representative three papers which I refer to in my
work, and the name of these papers will be listed in the end. Briefly, paper [1]
introduces three different array structures, which are uniform linear arrays(ULA),
uniform circular arrays(UCA), and uniform rectangular arrays(URA); Paper [2] applies
MUSIC algorithm in the planar array antenna; Paper [3] analyzes the performance of
MUSIC and ESPRIT DOA estimation for adaptive array smart antenna in mobile
communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-expectation:fb01a2df35ea3e36db0979b4f08f3ad1&#34;&gt;3.Expectation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my paper, firstly, I plan to make an introduction to smart antenna. Secondly, I
will derive array steering vectors and signals that antenna array receive for different
array structures, for example, ULA, UCA, URA in my own word, and make them more
generalized. Thirdly, I will introduce the importance of DOA estimation and MUSIC
algorithm. Next, verifying MUSIC algorithm for different situations is necessary and
compare them from different perspectives. At last, I will make a short summary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-references:fb01a2df35ea3e36db0979b4f08f3ad1&#34;&gt;4.References&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[1]L. Jin, L. Li, and H. Wang, &amp;ldquo;Investigation of Different Types of Array Structures for
Smart Antennas,&amp;rdquo; IEEE International conference on Microwave and Millimeter Wave
Technology, vol. 3, pp. 1160 - 1163, 2008&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[2]C. Sun, “The application of MUSIC algorithm in the planar array antenna,”2015 IEEE International Conference on Signal Processing, Communications and Computing
(ICSPCC),pp. 1 - 4, 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[3]T.B. LAVATE, V.K. KOKATE, A. M. SAPKAL, “Performance Analysis of MUSIC and
ESPRIT DOA Estimation algorithms for adaptive array smart antenna in mobile
communication,&amp;rdquo; 2010 Second International Conference on Computer and Network
Technology (ICCNT), pp. 308 - 311, 2010&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name:Dou Xin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Student ID:13010199053&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email:1161327784@qq.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PDF版：&lt;a href=&#34;http://douxin13.github.io/douxin.pdf&#34;&gt;douxin.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>